http://www.fisglobal.com/privacy

ISO
VAR (Value Added Resellers)
ISV (Independent Software Vendor)
Need Support
Worldpay is now FIS. Your experience is our top priority. We’re here to help.
Get support
Need Support
Worldpay is now FIS. Your experience is our top priority. We’re here to help.
Explore the Marketplace
FIS Modern Banking PlatformAdvance your bank with a modern core platform.
Click here
Data Restore
Protection from disaster.
Click here
Code Connect
The power of APIs with the scale of FIS.
Click here
Need Support
Worldpay is now FIS. Your experience is our top priority. We’re here to help.
Explore the Marketplace
InvestranData Exchange Solutions.
Click here
IFRS17The right strategy for transformation.
Click here
Commercial LendingSpeed up the decision process.
Click here
Need Support
Worldpay is now FIS. Your experience is our top priority. We’re here to help.
Need Support
Worldpay is now FIS. Your experience is our top priority. We’re here to help.
Need Support
Worldpay is now FIS. Your experience is our top priority. We’re here to help.
Get support
Search
FIS uses cookies to improve your experience on our websites. We use your browsing data on fisglobal.com to gather analytics to help provide personalized content and an overall better user experience. This helps us improve your experience for future visits to our site. Click here to continue to fisglobal.com/gdpr.
Do Not Track
I understand, continue
Privacy
FIS is committed to protecting the privacy and security of all personal information that we process in order to provide services to our clients.
FIS' clients, employees, vendors, partners and visitors provide us with significant amounts of personal information and protecting the privacy and security of this personal information is critical to FIS.
FIS has a Privacy Policy
that applies to all affiliates and employees worldwide. This program helps us ensure that personal information is handled properly. The Privacy Policy governs personal information collected by FIS for its own purposes as well as information provided to us as a data processor for our clients. It concerns the protection of information collected online as well as offline.
For specific information on how FIS protects personal information online, as well as information on submitting requests, please see the FIS Online Privacy Notice.
For clients based outside of the United States, their customers’ personal information may be transferred to FIS affiliates and data processers in the United States and elsewhere in the world. FIS will always protect the privacy and security of this personal information, regardless of where it is processed. Personal information transfers from the European Economic Area and other countries with data transfer restrictions will be authorized by approved model contracts, or other appropriate means.
FIS is also committed to transparency. We want everyone to understand how we collect and use personal information so they can interact with FIS with confidence. The links below can help you find the information you need about privacy and FIS. If you have any other questions, please contact the Privacy Office at privacyoffice@fisglobal.com.
FIS Privacy Policy
+
Download English PDF
Download French PDF
Online Privacy Notice
+
Download English PDF
Download French PDF
Let's Talk
Together, we can work to solve your business goals. Feel free to call +1 877.776.3706 now or provide your email address below and a representative will reach out to you soon.
Contact Us
ADVANCING THE WAY THE WORLD
PAYS, BANKS AND INVESTS
Let's start a
conversation
Let's work together to reach your goals. Contact us at the links below and a representative will be in touch.
We are here to help you and your business. Contact us using the button below.
©2020 FIS. Advancing the way the world pays, banks and invests™
